let questions = [
    {
        numb: 0,
        question: "Ready to take the quiz again?",
        answer: "YES, I AM READY!",
        options: [
            "YES, I AM READY!",
            "NO",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Faraday proposed that the alteration of electric and magnetic fields, generating and propelling each other in space, can be thought of as a form of moving energy.",
        answer: "False",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Michael Faraday showed how a current carrying wire behaves like a magnet.",
        answer: "False",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "André-Marie Ampère conducted experiments to clarify the connection between electric current and magnetism, exploring the behavior of electric currents in different conductors.",
        answer: "True",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Maxwell's Law describes mathematically the magnetic force between two electrical currents.",
        answer: "False",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Michael Faraday discovered electromagnetism in 1821. By 1831, he achieved electromagnetic induction, generating an electrical current from a changing magnetic field.",
        answer: "True",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Faraday found that when an electrical current passed through a coil, no additional current was generated in a nearby coil.",
        answer: "False",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Michael Faraday known as the father of electromagnetism.",
        answer: "False",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "James Clerk Maxwell is the father of electricity.",
        answer: "False",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "James Clerk Maxwell contributed in developing equations that showed the relationship of electricity and magnetism.",
        answer: "True",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Heinrich Hertz showed experimental evidence of electromagnetic waves and their link to light.",
        answer: "True",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "Accelerating electrons do not produce electromagnetic waves.",
        answer: "False",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "According to increasing frequency, the EM spectrum includes: radio waves, microwaves, infrared, visible light, ultraviolet, X-rays, and gamma rays.",
        answer: "True",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "Among the EM waves, the radio waves have photons of high energies while gamma rays have photons with the lowest energies.",
        answer: "False",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "The electromagnetic spectrum is a continuum of electromagnetic waves arranged according to frequency and wavelength.",
        answer: "True",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "The different types of electromagnetic waves are defined by the amount of energy carried by/possessed by the photons. Photons are bundles of wave energy.",
        answer: "True",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False" 
        ]
    },

    ]